stussy.com 2019-04-16

# Privacy Policy | Stussy | Official Website USA & Canada

This Privacy Policy is provided to explain how information is collected on our website and how that information is handled once it has been collected. Please note that this Privacy Policy may change at any time. While using the Stussy.com website you accept the terms and conditions outlined in this privacy policy and the terms of use.

REGISTRATION

Personal information is gathered by Stussy.com during the order checkout process. During the checkout process, your name, address, e-mail address, telephone number and payment information is collected. You also have the option of setting up an account to store personal information at which time a username and password are collected as well. Please note that your user name is you email address and you are able to create your own unique username. If you forget ior lose your password you can have it resent and the new password will be emailed to the address on file. For security reasons Stussy.com does not store sensitive credit card information on our servers. To view your account history, click My Account at any time to view your Stussy.com order history and track the status of your orders placed online. In order to view the information in the My Account section of the site you must first log in using your username and password. Remember your username is your email address.

UPDATING PERSONAL INFORMATION

Log onto stussy.com and click My Account to update your personal information online. If you have lost or do not remember your password, then please send an email from the email address you used to register your account. We will only send password information to the email address listed under the account. Password information will not be given out over the phone.

INFORMATION USAGE

The information collected during registration is used primarily to process and ship your order. Stussy.com will periodically update customers via email about new product updates and promotions. If you wish to be removed from this email list, then please visit stussy.com and remove your email address or email info@stussy.com with “remove email address” written in the subject or body. Your account information is maintained privately on our secure web servers. Stussy.com does not sell, share or rent email address and does not condone unsolicited email. Stussy.com will disclose such information in response to law enforcement agency’s request. Remember, Stussy.com will not use or transfer the personal information provided to us in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you with an opportunity to opt out of these unrelated uses.

COOKIES

Cookies are small text files that are stored on your computer’s hard drive and used by Stussy.com to enhance your shopping experience by speeding up the browsing experience and website performance. Cookies are also used to personalize your experience while using the Stussy .com website and remembering your information when you return to the Stussy.com website. This functionality is activated when the “Remember Me” check box is clicked. To turn this functionality off, simply uncheck the “Remember Me” check box.

SECURITY

The security of the information regarding your order is very important to us. We use the 128-bit Secure Socket Layer protocol to protect the security of your online order information. You can be assured that all sensitive information will be handled with discretion. SSL technology encrypts your order information to protect it from being decoded by anyone other than Stussy.com. Once you enter the checkout page your computer will being communicating with our server in secure mode. You can tell that you are in the secure mode by the “http” in the web address will be replaced by “https”. Depending on the browser, you will see either a padlock (Microsoft Internet Explorer, AOL, Netscape Communicator) or a solid key (Netscape Navigator) in the lower section of the browser window. Only browsers that use the 128-bit Secure Socket Layer protocol are able to order through the Stussy.com website. If your browser does not support SSL, please upgrade your browser.
